Edwin Ramos

edwin.ramos13@qmail.cuny.edu

DETAILS

(929) 370-7209

PROFILE

Current Queens College Computer Science Major with a current GPA above 3.5. Experienced with JavaScript, Typescript, C++, Python and more. Professional experience with Web Development as an Intern at a non-profit org. Experienced in several team environments and cultures across multiple industries.

LINKS

Personal Website

Github Profile

INTERNSHIPS

Web Development Intern, Lighthouse Guild

Dec 2019 — Apr 2020, New York City, NY

- Participated in ongoing development of new project web app in React.JS
- Made UI and Backend adjustments to current site and company tools using Javascript and PHP to improve User/Company Experience.
- Implemented bug fixes and delivered reports concerning them according to company policies.

TECHNICAL SKILLSET

Git

Node.js

SQL

React

CSS

HTML5

C++

Java

JavaScript

Python

Typescript

Ruby

React Native

Ruby on Rails

EDUCATION

CUNY Queens College, Computer Science, BS

Jan 2020 — Present, Flushing, NY

• Current GPA: 3.67

• Expected Graduation: Fall 2022

CUNY Queensborough Community College, Liberal Arts, AA

Jan 2016 — May 2018, Bayside, NY

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Logisitics Associate, Target Inc.

Jul 2018 — Present, Elmhurst, NY

- Worked with other team members and leaders to ensure smooth daily operations
- Performed a variety of backroom and store tasks to provide great customer experience
- Quickly cross-trained to fulfill store needs and deficiency of staffing in certain departments

Backroom Associate, Toys R Us

Oct 2017 — Jun 2018, Long Island City, NY

- Maintained and stocked sales floor and warehouse to company standards
- Fulfilled online orders for in-store pickup and shipment using various technologies